Guide to the Native American subject vertical file [ca.1850-2000.]
Native American subject vertical file
- Language - Piro (Peru, Ecuador) (Box 65)
- Language - Pokonchi (Mayan) (Box 65)
- Language - Ponca (Box 65)
- Language - Popoloca (Mexico) (Box 65)
- Language - Puelche (Patagonia, Argentina) (Box 65)
- Language - Puinave (Box 65)
- Language - Quiche (Mayan) (Box 65)
- Language - Quinault (Washington State) (Box 65)
- Language - Quinnipiac (Box 66)
- Language - Rama (Nicaragua) (Box 66)
- Language - Salish (Box 66)
- Language - Salishan (Box 66)
- Language - Salivan (Box 66)
- Language - Sarsi (Athapascan) (Box 66)
- Language - Seminole (Box 66)
- Language - Seneca (Box 66)
- Language - Shastan - See also: Language - Achomawi (Box 66)
- Language - Shoshonean (Box 66)
- Language - Siouan (Box 66)
- Language - South America 1 (Box 66)
- Language - South America 2 (Box 66)
- Language - Southwest (Box 66)
- Language - Spokane (Box 66)
- Language - Subtiaba (Nicaragua) (Box 66)
- Language - Taino (Box 66)
- Language - Takelma (Box 66)
- Language - Tanoan (Box 66)
- Language - Tapiete (Gran Chaco) (Box 66)
- Language - Tapuyah (Eastern Brazil) (Box 66)
- Language - Tarahumare (Mexico) (Box 66)
- Language - Tarsacan (Mexico) (Box 66)
- Language - Tehuelche (Patagonia, Argentina) (Box 66)
- Language - Tepehuane (Mexico) (Box 66)
- Language - Terreba (Costa Rica) (Box 66)
- Language - Tete de Baule (Box 66)
- Language - Tewa (Box 66)
- Language - Tigua (Box 66)
- Language - Timote (Colombia) (Box 66)
- Language - Timucua (Box 66)
- Language - Tinne (Athapascan) (Box 66)
- Language - Tlingit (Box 66)
- Language - Toba (Gran Chaco) (Box 66)
- Language - Totonac (Mexico) (Box 66)
- Language - Tsimshian (Box 66)
- Language - Tubatulabal (Box 66)
- Language - Tucanoan (Brazil) (Box 66)
- Language - Tucuna (Brazil) (Box 66)
- Language - Tupi - Guarani (Brazil) 1 (Box 66)
- Language - Tupi - Guarani (Brazil) 2 (Box 66)
- Language - Tutelo (Box 66)
- Language - Tzeltal (Box 66)
- Language - Tzotzil (Mexico) (Box 66)
- Language - Uru (Bolivia) (Box 66)
- Language - Ute (Box 66)
- Language - Uto Aztechan (Box 66)
- Language - Vaniva (Venezuela) (Box 66)
- Language - Venezuela (Box 66)
- Language - Virginia (Box 66)
- Language - Waicuri (Mexico) (Box 66)
- Language - Wakashian - See also: Language: Kwakiutl, Nootka (Box 66)
- Language - Warrau (Venezuela) (Box 66)
- Language - Winnebago (Box 66)
- Language - Wintun (Box 66)
- Language - Witoto (Colombia) (Box 66)
- Language - Wiyat (Wiyot) (Box 66)
- Language - Words, Numerals 1 (Box 67)
- Language - Words, Numerals 2 (Box 67)
- Language - Xinca (Central America) (Box 67)
- Language - Yahgan (Tierra del Fuego) (Box 67)
- Language - Yana (Box 67)
- Language - Yaqui (Mexico) (Box 67)
- Language - Yokuts (Box 67)
- Language - Yucatec (Box 67)
- Language - Yuchi (Box 67)
- Language - Yukian (Box 67)
- Language - Yuman - See also: Language Mohave, Diegueno (Box 67)
- Language - Yurok (Box 67)
- Language - Zaparo (Ecuador) (Box 67)
- Language - Zapotec (Mexico) (Box 67)
- Language - Zuni (Box 67)
- Latin American Indians (Box 67)
- Laws, etc. (Box 67)
- Laws, public (Box 132)
  Relating to Indians enacted by the 94th Congress.
- Leather (Box 67)
- Lecturers (Box 133)
- Legal remedies (Box 67)
- Legal status (Rights) 1 (Box 67)
- Legal status (Rights) 2 (Box 67)
- Legal status (Rights) 3 (Box 67)
- Legal status Articles & Corresp. 1 (Box 67)
- Legal status Articles & Corresp. 2 (Box 67)
- Legislation (Box 67)
- Libraries 1 (Box 67)
- Libraries 2 (Box 67)
- Libraries 3 (Box 67)
- Libraries 4 (Box 67)
- Libraries 5 (Box 68)
- Libraries 6 (Box 68)
- Libraries - Articles & Corresp. 1 (Box 68)
- Libraries - Articles & Corresp. 2 (Box 68)
- Libraries - Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery (Box 68)
- Libraries - Huntington Free Library (Box 68)
- Libraries - Indian 1 (Box 68)
- Libraries - Indian 2 (Box 68)
- Libraries - Library of Congress 1 (Box 68)
- Libraries - Library of Congress 2 (Box 133)
- Libraries - Metropolitan Museum (Box 68)
- Libraries - Morgan Library, N.Y. (Box 68)
- Libraries - National Indian Law Library (Box 68)
- Libraries - Newberry (Box 68)
- Libraries - NYC (Box 68)
- Literature, Poetry, etc. - See also Folklore; Periodicals, Indian (Box 68)
- Louisiana (Box 68)
- Louisiana - Antiquities (Box 68)
- Louisiana - Antiquities - Articles & Corresp (Box 68)
- Louisiana - Bibliography (Box 68)
- Louisiana - History (Box 68)
- Louisiana - Oversize (Box 130)
  An abstract from the records of John Sibley, esq. Indian agent in the territory of Orleans for the year 1807 relative to Indian affairs. (bound photostats)
- Louisiana - Indians - See also: Missions, Louisiana (Box 68)
- Luiseno Indians (Box 133)
  Geronimo Boscana, Chinigchinich / a historical account of the origins, customs and traditions of the Indians at the missionary establishment of St. Juan Capistrano, Alta, California, called the Acagchemen nation, 1846, photostats.
- Luiseno Indians (Shoshoni) - See also Language: Luiseno (Box 68)
- Luiseno Indians - Legislation and Misc. (Box 68)
- Lumbee Indians (Box 68)
- Lummi Indians (Box 68)
- Mahikan Indians (Algonquian) - See also Language: Mahican (Box 68)
- Maidu Indians - See also Language: Maidu (Box 68)
- Maidu Indians - Articles & Corres. (Box 68)
- Maine (Box 68)
- Maine - Antiquities 1 (Box 68)
- Maine - Antiquities 2 (Box 68)
- Maine - History (Box 68)
- Maine - Indians 1 (Box 68)
- Maine - Indians 2 (Box 68)
- Maine Indians - Articles & Corres. (Box 68)
- Maize 1 (Box 69)
- Maize 2 (Box 69)
- Makah Indians (Wakashan) (Box 69)
- Makah Indians - Legal Documents (Box 69)
- Malecite Indians (Box 69)
- Manahoac Indians (Algonquian) (Box 69)
- Mandan Indians (Siouan) (Box 69)
- Maps (Box 69)
- Maps, Indian 1 (Box 69)
- Maps, Indian 2 (Box 69)
- Mapuche Indians (Box 69)
- Maricopa Indians (Yuman) (Box 69)
- Maryland (Box 69)
- Maryland - Antiquities (Box 69)
- Maryland - History (Box 69)
- Maryland - Indians (Box 69)
- Mashpee Indians (Box 69)
- Masks 1 (Box 69)
- Masks 2 (Box 69)
- Masks 3 (Box 69)
- Massachusetts (Box 69)
- Massachusetts - Antiquities 1 (Box 69)
- Massachusetts - Antiquities 2 (Box 69)
- Massachusetts - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. (Box 69)
- Massachusetts - History 1 (Box 69)
- Massachusetts - History 2 (Box 69)
- Massachusetts - Indians - See also Missions: Massachusetts (Box 69)
- Mataco Indians (Gran Chaco) - See also: Folklore: Mataco; Language: Mataco (Box 69)
- Mathematics (Box 69)
- Matinecock Indians (Box 69)
- Matlatzinca. Indians (Mexico) - See also: Language: Matlatzinca (Box 69)
- Mattaponi Indians (Box 69)
- Maya 1 (Box 69)
- Maya 2 (Box 69)
- Maya 3 (Box 70)
- Maya 4 (Box 70)
- Maya 5 (Box 70)
- Maya 6 (Box 70)
- Maya 7 (Box 70)
- Maya 8 (Box 70)
- Maya 9 (Box 70)
- Maya - Articles & Corresp. 1 (Box 70)
- Maya - Articles & Corresp. 2 (Box 70)
- Maya - Antiquities 1 (Box 70)
- Maya - Antiquities 2 (Box 70)
- Maya - Antiquities - Articles & Corresp. (Box 70)
- Maya - Art (Box 70)
- Maya - Astronomy (Box 70)
- Maya - Calendars 1 (Box 70)
- Maya - Calendars 2 (Box 70)
- Maya - Calendars 3 (Box 70)
- Maya - Calendars 4 (Box 70)
- Maya - Calendars 5 (Box 70)
- Maya - History (Box 70)
- Maya - Indians (Box 70)
- Maya - Linguistics (Box 70)
- Maya - Manuscripts 1 (Box 70)
- Maya - Manuscripts 2 (Box 70)
- Maya - Manuscripts 3 (Box 71)
- Maya - Manuscripts 4 (Box 71)
- Maya - Manuscripts 5 (Box 71)
- Maya - Manuscripts - Articles & Corresp. (Box 71)
- Maya - Oversize (Box 130)
- Maya - Religion (Box 71)
- Maya - Textiles (Box 71)
- Maya - Writing (Box 71)
- Mazateco Indians (Mexico) (Box 71)
- Medals and Coins (Box 71)
- Media (Box 71)
- Medicine and Medicine Men 1 - See also: Deformities, artificial; Health and Disease; Shamans; Surgery, primitive (Box 71)
- Medicine and Medicine Men 2 (Box 71)
- Medicine and Medicine Men 3 (Box 71)
- Medicine and Medicine Men 4 (Box 71)
- Medicine and Medicine Men - Articles & Corresp. (Box 71)
- Medicine Wheels (Box 71)
- Melungeons (Box 71)
- Men (Box 71)
- Menominee Indians 1 (Box 71)
- Menominee Indians 2 (Box 71)
- Menominee Indians - Articles & Corres. (Box 71)
- Mesoamerica (Box 71)
- Metals and Metalwork (Box 72)
- Metals and Metalwork - Articles & Corres. & Misc. (Box 72)
- Metals and Metalwork - Bibliographies (Box 72)
- Metals and Metalwork - Copper (Box 72)
- Metals and Metalwork - Gold (Box 72)
- Metals and Metalwork - Metallurgy (Box 72)
- Metals and Metalwork - Silver (Box 72)
- Metis (Box 72)
- Mexico 1 (Box 72)
- Mexico 2 (Box 72)
- Mexico 3 (Box 73)
- Mexico - Articles & Corres. (Box 73)
- Mexico - Antiquities 1 (Box 73)
- Mexico - Antiquities 2 (Box 73)
- Mexico - Antiquities 3 (Box 73)
- Mexico - Antiquities - Oversize 1 (Box 132)
- Mexico - Antiquities - Oversize 2 (Box 132)
- Mexico - Antiquities - Oversize 3 (Box 132)
- Mexico - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. 1 (Box 73)
- Mexico - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. 2 (Box 73)
- Mexico - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. 3 (Box 73)
- Mexico - Antiquities - State of Chiapas (Box 73)
- Mexico - Art (Box 73)
- Mexico - History (Box 74)
- Mexico - History - Conquest (Box 132)
  Juan Jaramillio, Relacion hecha por el Capitan Juan Jaramillo, de la jornada que habia hecho a la tierra nueva en nueva españa y al descubrimiento de Cibola, yendo por General Francisco Vazquez Coronado Typescript.
- Mexico - Indians (Box 74)
- Mexico - Indians - Articles & Corres. (Box 74)
- Mexico - Oversize (Box 130)
- Mexico - State of Baja California (Box 74)
- Mexico - State of Campeche (Box 74)
- Mexico - State of Chiapas - Palenque (Box 74)
- Mexico - State of Chiapas - Articles & Corres. (Box 74)
- Mexico - State of Chihuahua (Box 74)
- Mexico - State of Colima (Box 74)
- Mexico - State of Durango (Box 74)
- Mexico - State of Guanajato (Box 74)
- Mexico - State of Guerrero (Box 74)
- Mexico - State of Hidalgo (Box 74)
- Mexico - State of Jalisco (Box 74)
- Mexico - State of Mexico 1 (Box 74)
- Mexico - State of Mexico 2 (Box 74)
- Mexico - State of Mexico 3 (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Mexico 4 (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Mexico 5 (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Mexico - Articles & Corres. (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Michoacan 1 (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Michoacan 2 (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Michoacan - Articles & Corres. (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Morelos 1 (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Morelos 2 (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Nayarit (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Nuevo Leon (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Oaxaca 1 (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Oaxaca 2 (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Oaxaca 3 (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Oaxaca 4 (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Oaxaca - Articles & Corres. 1 (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Oaxaca - Articles & Corres. 2 (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Pueblo (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Pueblo - Articles & Corres. (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Quintana Roo (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Quintana Roo - Articles & Corres. (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of San Luis Potosi (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Sinaloa (Box 75)
- Mexico - State of Sonora (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Sonora - Articles & Corres. (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Tabasco (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Tabasco - Articles & Corres. (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Tamaulipas (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Teotihuacan (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Tlaxcala (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Vera Cruz 1 (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Vera Cruz 2 (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Vera Cruz 3 (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Vera Cruz 4 (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Vera Cruz - Articles & Corres. (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Vera Cruz - Oversize (Box 130)
- Mexico - State of Yucatan 1 (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Yucatan 2 (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Yucatan 3 (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Yucatan 4 (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Yucatan 5 (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Yucatan 6 (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Yucatan 7 (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Yucatan 8 (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Yucatan - Articles & Corresp. (Box 76)
- Mexico - State of Zacatecas (Box 76)
- Miami Indians (Box 77)
- Miccosukee Indians (Box 77)
- Michigan (Box 77)
- Michigan - Antiquities 1 (Box 77)
- Michigan - Antiquities 2 (Box 77)
- Michigan - Antiquities - Articles & Corresp. (Box 77)
- Michigan History (Box 77)
- Michigan Indians (Box 77)
- Michigan Indians - Articles & Corresp. (Box 77)
- Micmac Indians (Box 77)
- Microfilming (Box 77)
- Microfilms (Box 77)
- Microforms (Box 77)
- Middle America (Box 77)
- Military Service (Box 77)
- Military and Trading Posts 1 (Box 77)
- Military and Trading Posts 2 (Box 77)
- Military and Trading Posts - Articles & Corresp. (Box 77)
- Mineral resources (Box 77)
- Mineral rights (Box 77)
- Mingo Indians (Box 77)
- Minnesota (Box 78)
- Minnesota - Antiquities 1 (Box 78)
- Minnesota - Antiquities 2 (Box 78)
- Minnesota - Antiquities - Articles & Corresp. (Box 78)
- Minnesota - History (Box 78)
- Minnesota Indians (Box 78)
- Mission Indians - California 1 (Box 78)
- Mission Indians - California 2 (Box 78)
- Mission Indians - California Newspaper - Articles and Misc. (Box 78)
- Missions (Box 78)
- Missions - Alaska (Box 78)
- Missions - Apache Indians (Box 78)
- Missions - Arizona (Box 78)
- Missions - California (Box 78)
- Missions - Canada (Box 78)
- Missions - Catholic (Box 78)
- Missions - Catholic - Articles & Corres. (Box 78)
- Missions - Catholic - Franciscan (Box 78)
- Missions - Catholic - Jesuit (Box 78)
- Missions - Cherokee (Box 78)
- Missions - Cherokee - Oversize (Box 131)
- Missions - Chippewa (Box 78)
- Missions - Christian (Box 78)
- Missions - Connecticut (Box 79)
- Missions - Dakota Indians (Box 79)
- Missions - Florida (Box 79)
- Missions - Georgia (Box 79)
- Missions - Hopi (Box 79)
- Missions - Huron Indians (Box 79)
- Missions - Idaho (Box 79)
- Missions - Illinois (Box 79)
- Missions - Indiana (Box 79)
- Missions - Indiana 2 (Box 133)
  Timothy S. Smith, Missionary abominations unmasked, or a view of Carey Mission...under the superintendance of the Rev. Isaac McCoy, 1833, photostats.
- Missions - Iowa (State) (Box 79)
- Missions - Kentucky (Box 79)
- Missions - Louisiana (Box 79)
- Missions - Massachusetts (Box 79)
- Missions - Michigan (Box 79)
- Missions - Minnesota (Box 79)
- Missions - Navajo (Box 79)
- Missions - New England (Box 79)
- Missions - New Mexico (Box 79)
- Missions - New York State (Box 79)
- Missions - North Dakota (Box 79)
- Missions - Oklahoma (Box 79)
- Missions - Onondaga Indians (Box 79)
- Missions - Oregon (Box 79)
- Missions - Ottowa Indians (Box 79)
- Missions - Papago (Box 79)
- Missions - Pennsylvania (Box 79)
- Missions - Pima Indians (Box 79)
- Missions - Protestant (Box 79)
- Missions - Protestant Congregational (Box 79)
- Missions - Protestant Episcopal (Box 79)
- Missions - Protestant Methodist, Episcopal (Box 79)
- Missions - Protestant Moravian (Box 79)
- Missions - Protestant Presbyterian (Box 79)
- Missions - Protestant Presbyterian - Articles & Corres. (Box 79)
- Missions - Pueblo (Box 79)
- Missions - Seminole Indians (Box 79)
- Missions - Shawnee Indians (Box 79)
- Missions - Sioux (Box 79)
- Missions - South America (Box 79)
- Mission - South Dakota (Box 79)
- Mission - Southwest (Box 79)
- Missions - Texas (Box 79)
- Missions - Wisconsin (Box 79)
- Mississippi - History (Box 79)
- Mississippi - Indians (Box 79)
- Mississippi - Roads (Box 79)
- Mississippi - State (Box 79)
- Mississippi Valley - Antiquities (Box 79)
- Missouri (State) - Antiquities 1 (Box 80)
- Missouri (State) - Antiquities 2 (Box 80)
- Missouri (State) - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. (Box 80)
- Missouri (State) - History (Box 80)
- Missouri Indians (Box 80)
- Missouri Valley (Box 80)
- Mistassini Indians (Box 80)
- Miwok Indians (Box 80)
- Mixes (Box 80)
- Mixtec Indians (Box 80)
- Mixtec Indians - Manuscripts (Box 80)
- Modoc Indians (Box 80)
- Mohave Indians (Box 80)
- Mohawk Indians 1 (Box 80)
- Mohawk Indians 2 (Box 80)
- Mohawk Indians - Iroquois (Box 80)
- Mohawk Indians - Canada (Box 80)
- Mohawk Indians - Gambling (Box 80)
- Mohawk Indians - Kanatsiohareke (Box 80)
- Mohave Indians - Language (Box 133)
  Church of England, Book of Common prayer in Mohawk, 1787, photostats.
- Mohawk Indians - Steelworkers (Box 80)
- Mohegan Indians (Box 81)
- Monaean Indians (Box 81)
- Mono Indians (Box 81)
- Montagnais - Naskapi Indians (Box 81)
- Montana (Box 81)
- Montana - Antiquities (Box 81)
- Montana - History (Box 81)
- Montana Indians (Box 81)
- Montauk Indians (Box 81)
- Moopa (Box 81)
- Mormon Church (Box 81)
- Mortuary Customs 1 (Box 81)
- Mortuary Customs 2 (Box 81)
- Mosquito Indians (Box 81)
- Motilone Indians (Box 81)
- Mounds and moundbuilders (Box 81)
- Moundville (Box 132)
- Muckleshoot (Box 81)
- Mummies (Box 81)
- Munsee - Delaware (Box 81)
- Museology 1 (Box 81)
- Museology 2 (Box 81)
- Museology - Articles & Corres. (Box 82)
- Museology - Bibliography (Box 82)
- Museology - Conservation (Box 82)
- Museums (Box 82)
- Museums and Anthropology (Box 82)
- Museums and Indians (Box 82)
- Museums - Alaska (Box 82)
- Museums - American Association of Museums (Box 82)
- Museums - American Indian Archaeological Institute (Box 82)
- Museums - American Museum of Natural History (Box 82)
- Museums - Anchorage Museum of History and Art (Box 82)
- Museums - Arizona (Box 82)
- Museums - Arkansas (Box 82)
- Museums - Basler Museum (Box 82)
- Museums - Boston Children’s Museum (Box 82)
- Museums - Brooklyn Museum (Box 82)
- Museums - Buffalo Bill Historical Center (Box 82)
- Museums - California (Box 82)
- Museums - Canada (Box 82)
- Museums - Central America (Box 82)
- Museums - Code Talker Museum (Box 82)
- Museums - Colombia (Box 82)
- Museums - Colorado (Box 82)
- Museums - Connecticut (Box 82)
- Museums - Cooper Hewitt (Box 82)
- Museums - Dartmouth (Box 82)
- Museums - Delaware (Box 82)
- Museums - Denver Art Museum (Box 82)
- Museums - Detroit Institute of Art (Box 82)
- Museums - Europe (Box 82)
- Museums - Field Museum of Natural History - Chicago, Illinois (Box 82)
- Museums - Five Civilized Tribes - Muskogee, Oklahoma (Box 82)
- Museums - Florida (Box 83)
- Museums - Fort Ticonderoga Museum, New York (Box 83)
- Museums - Georgia (Box 83)
- Museums - Gilcrease Institute of American History and Art (Box 83)
- Museums - Gorman, C.N. (Box 83)
- Museums - Great Britain (Box 83)
- Museums - Harvard University Peabody Museum (Box 83)
- Museums - Heard Museum, Phoenix, Arizona (Box 83)
- Museums - Hispanic Society (Box 83)
- Museums - Idaho (Box 83)
- Museums - Illinois (Box 83)
- Museums - Indian (Box 83)
- Museums - Indian Museum of North America (S.D.) (Box 83)
- Museums - Indiana (Box 83)
- Museums - Los Angeles County Museum (Box 83)
- Museums - Lowie Museum of Anthropology (Box 83)
- Museums - Maine (Box 83)
- Museums - Malki - California (Box 83)
- Museums - Maryland (Box 83)
- Museums - Mashpee Wampanoag (Box 83)
- Museums - Massachusetts (Box 83)
- Museums - Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York (Box 83)
- Museums - Mexico (Box 83)
- Museums - Michigan (Box 83)
- Museums - Millicent Rogers Museum (Box 83)
- Museums - Minnesota (Box 83)
- Museums - Mississippi (Box 83)
- Museums - Missouri - Articles & Corres. (Box 83)
- Museums - Montana (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of Indian Archaeology, London, England (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of Modem Art (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of Northern Arizona (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of Primitive Art (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - 1900 - 1949 (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - 1950 - 1987 (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - 1970 (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - 1990s (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of American Indian - Education (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Exhibits - 1959 (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Exhibits - 1960s (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Exhibits - 1970s (Box 83)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Exhibits - 1980 - 1983 (Box 84)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Exhibits - 1984 - 1986 (Box 84)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Exhibits - 1987 - 1988 (Box 84)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Exhibits - 1989 (Box 84)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Exhibits - Arctic Art - Eskimo Ivory (Box 84)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Exhibits - Echoes of the Drum (Box 84)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Exhibits - Glimpses at 1965 (Box 84)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Exhibits - Out of the Mists (Box 84)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Exhibits - Schedules (Box 84)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Inventory (Box 84)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - So the Spirit flows (Box 84)
- Museums - Museum of the American Indian - Star gods (Box 84)
- Museums - National Gallery (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian - Education (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian - Exhibitions (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian - Films (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian - History (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian - Misc. (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian - Programs, Schedules, and Calendars (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian - Promotional Materials, Membership (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian - Washington, D.C. (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian - Relocation - 1970's (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian - Relocation - 1980 - 1986 (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian - Relocation - 1987 - 1988 (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian - Relocation - 1989 (Box 84)
- Museums - National Museum of the American Indian - Staff (Box 84)
- Museums - Museum of the Cherokee Indian (Box 84)
- Museums - Native American Center for the Living Arts (Box 84)
- Museums - Navajo Tribal Museum (Box 84)
- Museums - Nebraska - Joslyn - Articles & Corres. (Box 84)
- Museums - Nevada (Box 84)
- Museums - New Brunswick, Canada (Box 84)
- Museums - New Hampshire (Box 84)
- Museums - New Jersey - Articles & Corres. (Box 84)
- Museums - New Mexico (Box 85)
- Museums - New York City (Box 85)
- Museums - New York 1 (Box 85)
- Museums - New York 2 (Box 85)
- Museums - Newark (Box 85)
- Museums - North Carolina (Box 85)
- Museums - North Dakota (Box 85)
- Museums - Ohio (Box 85)
- Museums - Oklahoma (Box 85)
- Museums - Oregon (Box 85)
- Museums - Panama (Box 85)
- Museums - Peale Museum, Philadelphia, PA (Box 85)
- Museums - Pennsylvania (Box 85)
- Museums - Pennsylvania University Museum (Box 85)
- Museums - Peru (Box 85)
- Museums - Philbrook Art Center, Tulsa, Oklahoma (Box 85)
- Museums - Provincial Museum, British Columbia (Box 85)
- Museums - Queens Museum (Box 85)
- Museums - Rhode Island (Box 85)
- Museums - Robert Hull Fleming Museum, Vermont (Box 85)
- Museums - Rochester Museum of Art and Sciences, New York (Box 85)
- Museums - Schoharia Museum of the Iroquois Indian (Box 85)
- Museums - Seneca Iroquois National Museum (Box 85)
- Museums - Smithsonian Institute, Washington, D.C. (Box 85)
- Museums - South America (Box 85)
- Museums - South Dakota (Box 85)
- Museums - Southern Plains Indian Museum and Crafts Center (Box 85)
- Museums - Southwest Museum, Los Angeles, CA 1 (Box 85)
- Museums - Southwest Museum, Los Angeles, CA 2 (Box 85)
- Museums - Spain (Box 85)
- Museums - Stewart Indian Museum (Box 85)
- Museums - Tennessee (Box 86)
- Museums - Texas (Box 86)
- Museums - Textile Museum (Box 86)
- Museums - United States National Museum (Box 86)
- Museums - Virginia (Box 86)
- Museums - Washington State (Box 86)
- Museums - Wheelwright (Box 86)
- Museums - Whitney (Box 86)
- Museums - Wisconsin (Box 86)
- Museums - Wyoming (Box 86)